i just want to expound on my last post um so like there's um it's it's not
what i'm realizing i don't know if realizing is even the right word that i want to use but
okay so sometimes people will be like well how can you be on how can you be on uh this app that
we know is a colonizer and then talk about colonizing and talk about use of energy etc etc
and what i'll say is that i am controlling how i use my energy on this app and that was not always
the case that was not always the case this app has become a tool
and the minute that it is no longer that thank you the minute that it is no longer that
i will adjust accordingly and you know i think that is a very important nuance however in contrast
you look at benito performing at and at the um at the halftime show now let me tell you something
i love baboni on a whole other level the executive producers of the nfl halftime show
are two of my very very very very good friends like family they literally produced my um what my my hbo
comedy special and i will not watch the halftime show now some might say well what do you think that is
what do you think that's valuable for the first time in my life i am being intentionable intentional
intentional i'm being intentional about every direction my energy is going knowing that there
are folks controlling it and in the past it was something that you may feel but because you didn't
have a direct um point of control you may have talked yourself out of it and the goal is always
to propagandize you out of believing what is the truth even propagandize you out of believing what you
feel so you're like well i may feel that but that feel crazy so forget it like i'm gonna just do whatever
however what i have come to understand and let me make it clear i did not know all the things that i
know i've learned them i didn't just show up i've learned them i did not show up knowing i learned them
okay and i learned them because i got over myself i got over my cringe of curiosity
and i really began to understand just how valuable i am and not of us not enough of us really understand
that on like an intrinsic level and we look at value as haughty we look at value as self-value as
arrogance we look at self-value as um as conceit when there is a difference
because when you really know yourself and you value yourself you you are not conceited because
conceit is a direction conceit is literally just projection like uh arrogance is insecurity
so i'm saying all of this to say that you will not see me watching the nfl you will not see me
um watching the grammy um watching the grammy's you know like i saw a video today with people at a
basketball game and they were losing their minds because denzel washington walked over to lebron james
losing their minds and i had to say to myself you know there is admiration and i get it and there's
reverence and i get it however at a certain point there's like obsession and there's this idea that
value for people is because they're talented value is because they are monetarily successful value is because
they have presented they have been leveled up as superior in stature maybe because of their
their skill or their build or their face etc and what i would say is i reserve my reverence for folks who
level up my vibration not for folks who are where they are because of a system that's in place
don't value me because i'm talented value me because of how i use my talents you understand what i'm saying
because i am multi-talented and i could be using my shit in a whole other direction if i wanted to
and so when we are looking at where we are placing our energy and where we are placing our attention
etc it doesn't have to be about like oh they're on some woo woo ba da ba like um crystal shit
this should just be regular shit bro this does not have to be like oh those are them kinds of people
i low-key get annoyed when i see the videos of the folks that think like this and they're doing it in
this way that feels like this is how they feel they have to present it to be taken seriously
because it don't gotta be different i'm a silly nigga bro okay and i'm i'm not gonna switch up
my silly nigganness even though i know what it is okay like i even started thinking do i need to
present more so like and i was like no no i won't i won't like i remember i had a psychic one time
that was doing all this extra shit and i was like bro chill chill chill we both psychic i know it don't
require none of that what you see from me bro it's like what do you see from me bro i don't need you to
do all of this flame shit whatever i know this is all what do you see from me and if you don't see
nothing today i understand because sometimes our shit don't pop off sometimes our shit don't turn on
do not make up no shit for me like i get it cut that flame off bro what do you see and if you don't
see nothing i'm still gonna pay you i'm still gonna pay you sometimes our shit does not turn on
i respect it so isabella i've been i've been clocking some lime green frames that i'm really
gonna have to come up on tomorrow so i'm just letting you know um so like i keep a set like
don't try to finesse me you're gonna piss me off really so i really just want to encourage all of
y'all to know that this knowledge is available to all of you no matter like how you show up
personality wise the only thing that is required is you showing up pure of heart that's it it's
showing up pure of heart showing up with clear intention that's all you don't got to be you don't
have to have your hair a certain way you can have a relaxer and and be tapped in you're gonna
eventually get out of the relaxer because the more tapped in you get you go realize like this
is actually affecting my tapenery however i just want to extend that to y'all because we have to
save ourselves and it's not going to be what you think it's not going to be what you think because
though violence is going to be necessary if you don't have the heart and the spirit on the other
side of it we're just going to continue the cycle and so my vision or my understanding of that
heart purification system that megos my egos is talking about um is really shifting again where
your energy goes what are you listening to what are you watching like and again i'm not saying anything
new i'm just saying it in a new time and i'm a new voice that's saying it and every spellcaster
that show up and add their energy to the to the incantation only increases its strength okay so
i just want y'all to to really like think about these things and even if you don't like get it right
away just keep thinking about it you know think about it like in in the shower think about it like
when you outside like just you know just think about it and let it marinate let it ruminate let
it move through you let it move through you you understand me so i ain't gonna be watching
benito this weekend i'm gonna i'm gonna have to run across clips online because i just can't i can't i
can't let them have my energy be a part of that concentration of energy they are literally
concentrating our energy in one place at one time and they are going to pull from that shit
so but these are and let me also add like part of my like ah it's not about me it's about like damn
like i i want to support benito but it's like no no this is not where you can be to get my support
i will give you my support in other ways but i can't give you you can't be there and have my energy
over there if that's the choice you make that's the choice you make but oh no but oh no i am not
on the tiktok i am not on the tiktok i am not on a tiktok i am not on the tiktok i am on the
scroll i am on the scroll see i am on the scroll see yes yes so you know
you know you know so that is you know that is the truth for me la verdad
you know so um i hope everybody has a good day and um baby have a beautiful day if you are working
for somebody or somewhere that is a drainer of your energy may they not get your energy today
may you produce the least amount of productivity for them that's possible for you to remain
employed to support yourself okay because really and truly fuck them
the city that's my photo that when you get to get to the party
da da da da da da da da da da da
Mwah!